<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:id="@+id/privacyRoot"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:padding="24dp"
    android:background="#101010">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tvPrivacy"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:textColor="@android:color/white"
        android:textSize="14sp"
        android:text="Privacy Policy\n\nLast updated: December 2025\n\nStress Buster Simulator respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how information is handled when you use our application.\n\nInformation Collection and Use\n\nStress Buster Simulator does not collect any personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, phone number, or precise location.\n\nThe app does not require users to create an account or log in.\n\nThird-Party Services\n\nThe app uses third-party services to support advertisements and app functionality.\n\nWe use Google AdMob to display banner, interstitial, and rewarded ads.\n\nGoogle AdMob may collect limited information such as:\n• Device information\n• Advertising ID\n• Approximate location\n• Ad interaction data\n\nThis information is used only to improve ad relevance and performance.\n\nAdvertisements\n\nStress Buster Simulator displays ads to keep the app free to use.\n\nRewarded ads are optional and shown only when the user chooses to watch them.\n\nChildren’s Privacy\n\nStress Buster Simulator does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.\n\nIf you believe that a child has provided personal data, please contact us and appropriate action will be taken.\n\nData Security\n\nWe do not store, share, or process personal user data on our servers.\n\nChanges to This Privacy Policy\n\nThis Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. Any changes will be reflected on this page.\n\nContact Us\n\nIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:\n\nstressbustersimulator@gmail.com" />

</ScrollView>
